http://www.alternateavenues.org/privacy-statement/

Skip to content
Statement of Privacy
Assure Pregnancy Clinic is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Assure Pregnancy Clinic Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Assure Pregnancy Clinic website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Assure Pregnancy Clinic collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Assure Pregnancy Clinic also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Assure Pregnancy Clinic. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Assure Pregnancy Clinic for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Assure Pregnancy Clinic Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Assure Pregnancy Clinic public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Assure Pregnancy Clinic does not read any of your private online communications.
Assure Pregnancy Clinic encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Assure Pregnancy Clinic so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Assure Pregnancy Clinic is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Assure Pregnancy Clinic and Assure Pregnancy Clinic family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Assure Pregnancy Clinic collects and uses your personal information to operate the Assure Pregnancy Clinic Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Assure Pregnancy Clinic also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Assure Pregnancy Clinic and its affiliates. Assure Pregnancy Clinic may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Assure Pregnancy Clinic does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Assure Pregnancy Clinic may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Assure Pregnancy Clinic may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Assure Pregnancy Clinic, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Assure Pregnancy Clinic does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Assure Pregnancy Clinic keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Assure Pregnancy Clinic, in order to determine what Assure Pregnancy Clinic services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Assure Pregnancy Clinic to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Assure Pregnancy Clinic Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Assure Pregnancy Clinic or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Assure Pregnancy Clinic; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Assure Pregnancy Clinic, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Assure Pregnancy Clinic Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Assure Pregnancy Clinic pages, or register with Assure Pregnancy Clinic site or services, a cookie helps Assure Pregnancy Clinic to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Assure Pregnancy Clinic Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Assure Pregnancy Clinic features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Assure Pregnancy Clinic services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Assure Pregnancy Clinic secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Assure Pregnancy Clinic secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Assure Pregnancy Clinic will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Assure Pregnancy Clinic encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Assure Pregnancy Clinic is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Assure Pregnancy Clinic welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Assure Pregnancy Clinic has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Assure Pregnancy Clinic at admin@assurepregnancy.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
English
English Spanish
